ewoss.net 2012-06-14

# eWoss Privacy Policy

eWoss Privacy Policy

**Introduction**

**eWoss** respects each individual's right to personal privacy. We will collect and use information through our Web site only in the ways disclosed in this statement. This statement applies solely to information collected at **eWoss's** Web site, www.eWoss.com.

**Administration**

Website Name: eWoss  
Address: 7415 W 130th St, Suite 100  
State: Kansas  
Zip Code: 66213  
Country: United States  
Website URL: [http://www.eWoss.com](http://www.ewoss.com/)  
Website Email: [info@eWoss.com](mailto:info@eWoss.com)

**Part 1. Information Collection & Usage**

**eWoss** collects information through our Web site at several points. We collect the following information about primary visitors to this Website: visitor's domain, visitor's IP address.

**IP Address** \- An IP address is a number that's assigned to Your computer whenever You surf the web. We retain Your IP address to help us diagnose any problems with our servers, to administer our Website, to help identify each visitor, to gather broad anonymous demographic information, to enforce compliance with **eWoss'** terms and conditions, and otherwise to protect services, customers, and others.

**Cookies** \- Cookies are small bits of electronic information that a website can transfer to a visitor's hard drive to help tailor and keep record of visits to our Website. The use of cookies is standard on the internet and many websites use them. Cookies allow website operators to better customize visits to the site. Although, eWoss does not currently utilize cookies on our Website, our third party advertising companies may, in fact, use them from time to time.

Although most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, You can usually change Your browser to prevent that or to notify You when You are sent a cookie. This gives You the option to accept or not accept cookies. If You would like more information on cookies, we suggest You visit <http://www.cookiecentral.com/>.

**Third Party Advertising** \- eWoss uses third-party advertising companies and advertising networks to serve ads and collect information when you visit our Website. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on this Website, other sites and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

**Part II. Compliance with Service or Process or Law Enforcement**

Occasionally **eWoss** may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide information related to our Website to the appropriate governmental authorities. We will disclose any such information upon receipt of an appropriate court order, subpoena, or to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation. **eWoss** fully cooperates with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal activities. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful.

**Part III. Third Party Links, Co-brand, Relationships, and Public Forums**

**eWoss** uses third-party advertising companies and advertising networks to serve ads and collect information when you visit our Website. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on this Website, other sites and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

**Part IV. Problem Resolution**

If problems arise, You and other visitors to our Website may contact **eWoss** by email. We are committed to resolving disputes within a reasonable time frame.

**Part V. Consent**

By using our Website, You consent to the collection and use of Your information by eWoss as set forth in this privacy statement. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that You will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what limited circumstances we disclose it. Continued access of the Website shall constitute acceptance of any modifications to this privacy statement.

This policy has been updated as of May 14, 2010.
